(All the right friends in all the right places)
So yeah we're going down
(All the right moves in all the right places)
Paint a picture of the perfect place
They've got it better than when anyone's told ya,
I'll be the King of Hearts, you're the Queen of Spades
And we'll fight for you like we were soldiers
I know we've got it good
But they've got it made
And the grass is getting greener each day
I know things are looking up
But soon they'll take us down
Before anybody's knowing our name
They've got all the right friends in all the right places
So yeah, we're going down
They've got all the right moves in all the right faces
Everybody knows, everybody knows where we're going
Yeah, we're going down
I said, everybody knows, everybody knows where we're going
Do you think I'm special, do you think I'm nice
Am I bright enough to shine in your spaces
Between the noise you hear and the sound you like
Are we just sinking in the ocean of faces
It can't be possible that rain can fall,
Only when it's over our heads
The sun is shining everyday, but it's far away
Over the world it's said, they've got, they've got
All the right friends, in all the right places
So yeah we're going down
We got all the right moves in all the right places
Everybody knows, everybody knows where we're going
Yeah, we're going down
Yeah, we're going down (going down, going down, going down, going down)
It don't matter what you see
I know I could never be
Someone that'll look like you
It don't matter what you say
I know I could never face
Someone that could sound like you
(All the right friends, in all the right places
So yeah we're going down
They got all the right moves in all the right places
So yeah we're going down)
(All the right friends, in all the right places
So yeah we're going down
They got all the right moves in all the right places
So yeah we're going down)
Said, everybody knows everybody knows where we're going
Yeah we're going down
I said, everybody knows everybody knows where we're going
Yeah we're going down (going down, going down, going down)
Yeah we're going down
(All the right moves, hey)